# **Zachary Upstone**

Email: Zac.upstone@gmail.com LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/zachary-upstone-076218214/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/zachary-upstone-076218214/</a>

Telephone: 07591 701760 Website: <a href="https://zupstn.com">https://zupstn.com</a>

# Personal Profile

I am a recent graduate with a 1<sup>st</sup> in Computer Science from the University of Bath. I have experience working in both software development and quality assurance at BSQUARE an IoT solutions company. From this, I also gained experience working within a team in an agile environment developing my communication skills. I also have experience working multiple customerfacing job at McDonalds and a bar making me into a adaptable and enthusiastic worker who is good at handling people. I am also a team worker having experience working on group projects throughout university, this also shows that I am reliable and trustworthy.

## Education

2020 - 2024

**University of Bath – Computer Science BSc – First Class Honours.**Overall grade – 74.51%

#### **Units including:**

- Final year project (Dissertation) 71% titled "Human Involvement Can Improve Current Image Synthesis Methods within the Domain of Art" explored using human feedback to improve underlying agents for image synthesis in a manner similar to ChatGPT, this was implemented in Python.
- Logic and semantics of programming languages 81% I studied how category theory relates to the underlying logic of programming languages, including the lambda calculus and closed cartesian categories.
- **Entrepreneurship** 72% As a team we started a company developing a business plan for a company selling services between a student community.
- Graphs and Networks: Theory and Applications 73%
- Reinforcement learning 71% In a group our team implemented DQN, RAINBOW and PPO in Python to solve the lunar lander environment in OpenAl's gym.
- Advanced graphics processing 89% From scratch I developed a ray tracer in C++, implementing reflection, refraction and other lighting effects, concluding with implementing photon mapping.
- **Safety-critical systems** 79% I studied case studies of how systems shortcoming in relation to safety in the past and how to mitigate or prevent such problems in the future.

2013 - 2020

### **Chesham Grammar School**

**A level:** Further Mathematics (A), Mathematics (A\*), Computer Science (A), Physics (A).

GCSE's: 4 grades 9's, 2 grade 8's, 3 grades 6's, 1 grade 5, 1 grade A.

### Work Experience

July 2022 - June 2023

- Student software developer at BSQUARE, during my degree, I had a yearlong placement at BSQUARE, in which I worked 6 months in the development team for SquareOne in which I fixed bugs, produced new features (such as an OS updates page and a tour for a product) and tested code during QA sprints and 6 months in the

	QA team in which I wrote automated tests (for API and UI), performed manual tests and managed the delegation of manual testing during the QA aprint
Nov 2021 - June 2022	testing during the QA sprint.  - Bar staff at the Students Union at the University of Bath, I dealt with customers requests serving drinks, cleaning and operating a till.
July 2021 - Oct 2021	<ul> <li>I had to use communication skills and be adaptable to new jobs.</li> <li>Crew member at McDonalds, I worked at multiple station in McDonalds showing flexibility and ability to work in a team. This required good communication within the team in case I was needed at different stations.</li> </ul>
July 2020 - Sept 2020	<ul> <li>Assistant Gardener at RM Gardening, this included manual labour and dealing with customers' requests developing my tenacity and adaptability to different workplace environments.</li> </ul>
Other Experience	
Nov 2018 - Mar 2020	<ul> <li>Volunteered at WorkAid a tool repair shop for 18 months, In which I learned to fix knitting machines and gained skills in organisation and problem solving.</li> </ul>
July 2019	<ul> <li>1 Week work experience at the Audit Bureau of Circulations in various departments reviewing magazines authenticity and managing IT issues which helped me understand how a team of people is coordinated.</li> </ul>
June 2018	<ul> <li>2 Weeks at the IT help desk at Close Brother Asset Management assisting with various jobs, including network problems, software installation/setup and sorting hardware appliances. This helped develop my team communication and people skills.</li> </ul>
<u>Technical skills</u>	
	<ul> <li>Experience with C++, Java and Python from my degree</li> <li>Experience with Angular (TS, HTML, CSS), Selenium, and Gherkin from BSQUARE</li> </ul>
	<ul> <li>Experience working in an agile environment and using Jira from BSQUARE</li> </ul>
	- Experience with <b>React</b> from personal projects and hackathons
	<ul> <li>Experience working in a team from McDonalds and BSQUARE</li> <li>Customer service skills from SU bar</li> </ul>
A 1.1	- Full UK driver's license
<u>Achievements</u>	Cold Doff in which become letted two control of the Cold Doff in which become letted two controls.
	<ul> <li>Gold DofE, in which I completed two expeditions hiking in the Brecon beacons and Snowdonia.</li> </ul>
	- Competed in BathHack 2021 and 2024 using React both times
	producing web games.
	- Employee of the month August 2021 at McDonalds
<u>Interests</u>	. ,
References	I have a keen interest in art and design producing prints using spray techniques as well as collages and clay sculptures. I am also interested in exercise going to the gym and swimming multiple times a week.
110101011003	Hannah Stainer Alan Hayes
	Operations manager at BSQUARE HannahS@bsquare.com Personal tutor at the University of Bath AH347@bath.ac.uk